<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Lego Art Creator</title><link>https://legoartcreator.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Lego Art Creator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:07:27 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://legoartcreator.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Legal</title><link>https://legoartcreator.com/legal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:11:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://legoartcreator.com/legal/</guid><description>Legal Disclaimer Affiliation Disclaimer
LegoArtCreator.com is an independent website and is not affiliated with, endorsed by, or sponsored by The LEGO Group or any of its affiliates. LEGO, the LEGO logo, and related trademarks and trade dress are the property of The LEGO Group, and they do not endorse or sponsor this website unless explicitly stated otherwise.
Disclaimer of Warranty and Liability
The information provided on legoartcreator.com (hereinafter referred to as "</description></item><item><title>Page or Resource Not Found</title><link>https://legoartcreator.com/404/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:09:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://legoartcreator.com/404/</guid><description> 404
Page not found Sorry, we couldn’t find the page you’re looking for.
Go back home</description></item><item><title>Cookies</title><link>https://legoartcreator.com/cookies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:07:47 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://legoartcreator.com/cookies/</guid><description>Cookie Policy Last updated: 10/14/23
1. What Are Cookies? Cookies are small text files that are stored on your device when you visit a website. They are widely used to make websites work or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to website owners.
2. How We Use Cookies We use cookies for the following purposes:
Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to collect anonymous data about how visitors use our website.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://legoartcreator.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:07:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://legoartcreator.com/contact/</guid><description> Contact Us Whether you have questions, suggestions, or just want to say hello, we'd love to hear from you!
Name Email Message Submit</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://legoartcreator.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:06:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://legoartcreator.com/privacy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy Last updated: 10/12/23
This Privacy Policy explains how [legoartcreator.com] ("we," "our," or "us") collects and protects your personal information when you visit our website and use our services. We respect your privacy and are committed to ensuring that your personal information remains confidential and secure.
1. Information We Collect We do not collect any personally identifiable information from visitors to our website. We may collect non-personal information, such as your IP address, browser type, and other technical information that is automatically transmitted by your device when you access our website.</description></item></channel></rss>